Finding Aid for Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated
Clarke Historical Library
- Central Michigan University Communications (UComm) Collection, 1946, 2018, and undated.
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dealing, James R., History,undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Debolt, Joseph,undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Debruin, Robert L.,undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dede, Alper,undated (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: DeGenova, Mary Kay,undated (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Delia, Thomas Joseph, Chemistry,undated (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: DeMeyer, Lisa,undated (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Demlow, Marilyn, Health Services,undated (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: DeKryger, William J., Industrial Education,undated (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Delong, Ann M.,undated (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dening, James W.,undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dennis, Larry,undated (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Deromedi, Herbert W., Physical Education,undated (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Deunk, Norman H., Jr., Business,undated (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Deyo, Diane,undated (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dilworth, David,undated (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dinan, John,undated (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dinius, Stanley,undated (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dinse, John H.,undated (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Divine, Richard,undated (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dixon, Barbara, Music,undated (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Doke, Kirt,undated (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dollard, Joan W.,undated (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dolley, Diane,undated (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Domina, Tanya,undated (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dominguez, Jesse,undated (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dominguez, Paul,undated (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Donn, Paul,undated (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Doran, Joy,undated (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Joy L. Doremire,undated (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dorrah, Harvey,undated (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Douglass, Claudia, Biology,undated (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Doyle, Randall,undated (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dressel, Janice Hartwick,undated (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Duffield, Holley G., English,undated (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dunbar, Gary, Psychology,undated (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dunham, R. William,undated (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Dunn, Carolyn,undated (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: George W. Dunn,undated (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ebel Charles, History,undated (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Eberly, Carole,undated (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ebner, Robert James,undated (Box 50, Folder 55)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Echelberger, Matthew,undated (Box 50, Folder 56)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ecker, Louis G. ,undated (Box 50, Folder 57)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Eddy, Pamela,undated (Box 50, Folder 58)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Edgar, Gerald,undated (Box 50, Folder 59)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Egler, Steven, Music,undated (Box 50, Folder 60)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Eiszler, Charles F., Jr.,undated (Box 50, Folder 61)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Eke, Maureen,undated (Box 50, Folder 62)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ellard, Al,undated (Box 50, Folder 63)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ellertson, Alan Kim,undated (Box 50, Folder 64)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Elliott, Gerald,undated (Box 50, Folder 65)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Elliott, Kathie,undated (Box 50, Folder 66)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: El-Sawi, Nehad,undated (Box 50, Folder 67)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Enarson, Cam E.,undated (Box 50, Folder 68)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Enberg, Dick,undated (Box 50, Folder 69)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Endres, Thomas J., Public Broadcasting,undated (Box 50, Folder 70)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: English, Ann Marie (Owens),undated (Box 50, Folder 71)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: English, Kristina,undated (Box 50, Folder 72)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Cora Enman,undated (Box 50, Folder 73)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Robert Enman, Music,undated (Box 50, Folder 74)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Daniel Enos,undated (Box 50, Folder 75)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Epstein, Adam,undated (Box 50, Folder 76)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ericksen, Donna,undated (Box 50, Folder 77)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Erzikoua, Elina,undated (Box 50, Folder 78)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Eskridge, Ann,undated (Box 50, Folder 79)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Evans, Jackie M., Elementary Education,undated (Box 50, Folder 80)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Eversole Daniel E.,undated (Box 50, Folder 81)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Eyers, Christina ,undated (Box 50, Folder 82)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fahlman, Bradley,undated (Box 50, Folder 83)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Bradley Fahr,undated (Box 50, Folder 84)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fairbanks, John, Business and Admission,undated (Box 50, Folder 85)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fairbanks, Michael, Biology,undated (Box 50, Folder 86)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Faleer, Robert,undated (Box 50, Folder 87)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Falls, Lisa,undated (Box 50, Folder 88)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Famoye, Felix,undated (Box 50, Folder 89)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fancher, Carlton, Health,undated (Box 50, Folder 90)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fanning, Robert,undated (Box 50, Folder 91)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Farley, Dennis Scott,undated (Box 50, Folder 92)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Farley, William E.,undated (Box 50, Folder 93)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fattah, Moataz,undated (Box 50, Folder 94)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Lynn Fauver,undated (Box 50, Folder 95)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Featheringham, Richard,undated (Box 50, Folder 96)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Felton, James Martin, Finance,undated (Box 50, Folder 97)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ferrer, Daniel,undated (Box 50, Folder 98)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fetzer, Joel,undated (Box 50, Folder 99)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fevig, David,undated (Box 50, Folder 100)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fields, D. Michael,undated (Box 50, Folder 101)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Finck, Joseph,undated (Box 50, Folder 102)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Frank E. Fishell, Math,undated (Box 50, Folder 103)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fisher, David R.,undated (Box 50, Folder 104)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fisher, John, S., Housing operations,undated (Box 50, Folder 105)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fitzgerald, Pamela,undated (Box 50, Folder 106)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fitzhenry, Jerome T., Journalism,undated (Box 50, Folder 107)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fitzpatrick, Charles J.,undated (Box 50, Folder 108)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Flanagan, Mary Jane,undated (Box 50, Folder 109)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fleming, Kirsten,undated (Box 50, Folder 110)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fleming, Mary Lu,undated (Box 50, Folder 111)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fleming, Richard Joseph,undated (Box 50, Folder 112)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Flory, Brenda,undated (Box 50, Folder 113)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Richard Ormano Flynn, HPER,undated (Box 50, Folder 114)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Foote, Jeffrey H.,undated (Box 50, Folder 115)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ford, Ray,undated (Box 50, Folder 116)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fornari, Marco,undated (Box 50, Folder 117)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Foster-Lifson, Rachel, Psychology,undated (Box 50, Folder 118)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fox, Richard W.,undated (Box 50, Folder 119)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Francek, Mark,undated (Box 50, Folder 120)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Frank, Martha,undated (Box 50, Folder 121)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fraser, Blanche,undated (Box 50, Folder 122)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Freling, Roger N., English,undated (Box 50, Folder 123)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Freeman, S. Gay,undated (Box 50, Folder 124)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Frey, Laura,undated (Box 50, Folder 125)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Frick, Hedwig Marie,undated (Box 50, Folder 126)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Friedman, Gary,undated (Box 50, Folder 127)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Friedrich, Douglas D.,undated (Box 50, Folder 128)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fries, Peter H.,undated (Box 50, Folder 129)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Frisch, John A.,undated (Box 50, Folder 130)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Frodge, Nedra,undated (Box 50, Folder 131)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Frost, Bruce,undated (Box 50, Folder 132)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fryda, Larry, IET,undated (Box 50, Folder 133)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Fubara, Ayayi,undated (Box 50, Folder 134)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gagnon, Gary,undated (Box 50, Folder 135)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Sue Gibbs Gamble, Music,undated (Box 50, Folder 136)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Ganoe, Cathy,undated (Box 50, Folder 137)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gardecki, Barrara L. Psychology,undated (Box 50, Folder 138)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gardner, Alice,undated (Box 50, Folder 139)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Garver, Michael,undated (Box 50, Folder 140)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gaskill, Peggy,undated (Box 50, Folder 141)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gaskill, Peggy,undated (Box 50, Folder 142)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gates-Duffield, Pamela,undated (Box 50, Folder 143)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gealt, Michael A.,undated (Box 50, Folder 144)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gehring, Thomas,undated (Box 50, Folder 145)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: George, Sharon L.,undated (Box 50, Folder 146)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gerkin, Holly,undated (Box 50, Folder 147)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gervin, Dennis,undated (Box 50, Folder 148)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Getahun, Solomon,undated (Box 50, Folder 149)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gibson, Bryan,undated (Box 50, Folder 150)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gilb, Tyra, Music,undated (Box 50, Folder 151)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gilbert, Michael,undated (Box 50, Folder 152)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gilchrist, Gordon H.,undated (Box 50, Folder 153)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gillingham, David,undated (Box 50, Folder 154)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gillingham, James, Biology,undated (Box 50, Folder 155)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gillingham, Mary,undated (Box 50, Folder 156)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: David B. Ginsberg,undated (Box 50, Folder 157)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Glasius, Erik,undated (Box 50, Folder 158)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Goduka, Ivy,undated (Box 50, Folder 159)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Goenner, James,undated (Box 50, Folder 160)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Goldsmith, Rae,undated (Box 50, Folder 161)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gonzales, Laura,undated (Box 50, Folder 162)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Goodrich, Elizabeth,undated (Box 50, Folder 163)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Goodwin, Megan Pauline,undated (Box 50, Folder 164)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: James Gordan,undated (Box 50, Folder 165)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gordan, Kelly Lynn,undated (Box 50, Folder 166)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gorsich, Steven W.,undated (Box 50, Folder 167)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gorton, Peter,undated (Box 50, Folder 168)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Goupell, Duane, OIR,undated (Box 50, Folder 169)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Grabinski, Roger Neil,undated (Box 50, Folder 170)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Grabinski, C. Joanne,undated (Box 50, Folder 171)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Grant, Edward,undated (Box 50, Folder 172)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Graves, Bennie,undated (Box 50, Folder 173)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Harold Graves,undated (Box 50, Folder 174)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Grawburg, Larry,undated (Box 50, Folder 175)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gray, Deborah,undated (Box 50, Folder 176)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gray, Pamela,undated (Box 50, Folder 177)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Green, Colleen,undated (Box 50, Folder 178)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Green, Denise,undated (Box 50, Folder 179)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Greenlund, Janice Ann,undated (Box 50, Folder 180)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Greenwood, Frank,undated (Box 50, Folder 181)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Griffiths, Ronald David,undated (Box 50, Folder 182)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Grossa, John, Jr., Geography,undated (Box 50, Folder 183)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Grossman, George William,undated (Box 50, Folder 184)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Guard, David,undated (Box 50, Folder 185)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Guerriero, Ana,undated (Box 50, Folder 186)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Guinn, Traci,undated (Box 50, Folder 187)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Gust, Dale D.,undated (Box 50, Folder 188)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Guy, Michael,undated (Box 50, Folder 189)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Haas, Carol,undated (Box 50, Folder 190)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Haddad, Angela,undated (Box 50, Folder 191)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Hadden, Lisa,undated (Box 50, Folder 192)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Haeger, John,undated (Box 50, Folder 193)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Hageman, James,undated (Box 50, Folder 194)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Hagens, Helen,undated (Box 50, Folder 195)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Haight, Sherrel,undated (Box 50, Folder 196)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Hakemi, Ahmad,undated (Box 50, Folder 197)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Hall, Mitchell,undated (Box 50, Folder 198)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Hall, Ruth,undated (Box 50, Folder 199)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Hall, Timothy,undated (Box 50, Folder 200)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Hallett, Bernice,undated (Box 50, Folder 201)
  - Faculty News Releases, D-H: Halpret, Richard,undated (Box 50, Folder 202)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Alice Hamacheck,undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hamas, Michael, Biology,undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hammel, Arnold Dean,undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hammer, Roger,undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Han, Henry H., Political Science,undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hancock, Merodie,undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: John Hansen,undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hanson, Elizabeth,undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Harding, Desmond,undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Harding, Scott,undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hardy, Richard, Health,undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Harris, Fred,undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Harrison, Julie,undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hartley, Richard L.,undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hartman, Gerald D.,undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hartman, John K.,undated (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hartshorne, Timothy Scotford,undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hastings, Charles,undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hatch, Roger, Religion,undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Haushalter, William,undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hayen, Roger,undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hayes, Randall Bryant,undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hayes, Rebecca,undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hazekamp, Donald W., Math,undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Alpha Psi Omega,undated (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Health, Phillis,undated (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Heeke, David,undated (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hein, Matthew,undated (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Heinze, Dyke,undated (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Helfrich, Janet S.,undated (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Helferich, Keith,undated (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hella, Lori,undated (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jerome D. Henderson,undated (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Henley, Mary,undated (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Henricks, Joyce,undated (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Henry, Maureen,undated (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Herd-Clark, Dawn,undated (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Herman, Nancy,undated (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Herman, William J., TV,undated (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hernandez, Paul,undated (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Herrera, Robert,undated (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hershey, David,undated (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hertzler, Philip,undated (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hess, George,undated (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Heuberger, Roschelle,undated (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Heumann, Benjamin,undated (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hicks, Troy,undated (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Higgins, Monte L., Educational,undated (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hildebrandt, Leslie,undated (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hill, James P., Political Science,undated (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hill, James Richard,undated (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hill, Mary,undated (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hinck, Edward,undated (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hinck, Shelly,undated (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hirschi, Stanley, Physics,undated (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hitch, Elizabeth,undated (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hixson, Michael,undated (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hodgson, Shu-Ping C.,undated (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Carolyn J Hoffman,undated (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hoffman, Holly,undated (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hoffman, John D.,undated (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hoffman, Robert E.,undated (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hohner, Robert,undated (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Holder, Stephen C.,undated (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Holland, Donald E.,undated (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Holmes, Monica,undated (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hood, William,undated (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hopp, Neil,undated (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Horoi, Mihai,undated (Box 51, Folder 69)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hornak, James E.,undated (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: N. Joan Hornak,undated (Box 51, Folder 71)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Horton, Dennis L., Music,undated (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hough, Robin,undated (Box 51, Folder 73)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Houghton, Nickolas,undated (Box 51, Folder 74)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: House-Gardner, Sharon,undated (Box 51, Folder 75)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Houston-Philpot, Kimberly,undated (Box 51, Folder 76)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hoard, Carole,undated (Box 51, Folder 77)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Howard, Michelle,undated (Box 51, Folder 78)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Howell, Bob, Chemistry,undated (Box 51, Folder 79)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Howell, James F., English,undated (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Howell, Marsha,undated (Box 51, Folder 81)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Howell, Sandra,undated (Box 51, Folder 82)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hu, Gongzhu,undated (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Huang, Zhenyu,undated (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hughes, Diana,undated (Box 51, Folder 85)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hunt, Thomas Michael,undated (Box 51, Folder 86)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hurtado, Luz Marcela,undated (Box 51, Folder 87)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hutslar, Karen,undated (Box 51, Folder 88)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hwang, Mark,undated (Box 51, Folder 89)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hyames, Jeff,undated (Box 51, Folder 90)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hyble Carol,undated (Box 51, Folder 91)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hyde, Linda,undated (Box 51, Folder 92)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Hynes, Frances,undated (Box 51, Folder 93)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Kimberly Ingebrigtson,undated (Box 51, Folder 94)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Ingersoll, Chris,undated (Box 51, Folder 95)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Inungu, Joseph (Jeff),undated (Box 51, Folder 96)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Ionin, Yury,undated (Box 51, Folder 97)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Irwin, James,undated (Box 51, Folder 98)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Islam, Didarul,undated (Box 51, Folder 99)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Ivanitskaya, Lana,undated (Box 51, Folder 100)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jackson, Jeannie,undated (Box 51, Folder 101)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jackson, Koblar Alan,undated (Box 51, Folder 102)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jackson, Mary-Garland,undated (Box 51, Folder 103)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jackson, Shirley,undated (Box 51, Folder 104)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jacob-Timm, Susan,undated (Box 51, Folder 105)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jacque, Mitchell,undated (Box 51, Folder 106)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jaeger, Anne M.,undated (Box 51, Folder 107)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jaffa, Melvyn,undated (Box 51, Folder 108)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jaksa, Stephen,undated (Box 51, Folder 109)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: James, Patricia,undated (Box 51, Folder 110)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Janis, Richard E.,undated (Box 51, Folder 111)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Janosky, Janine,undated (Box 52, Folder 112)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Randolph Jaques, Accounting,undated (Box 51, Folder 113)
  - Faculty News Releases, H-K: Jaquith, Charles E.,undated (Box 51, Folder 114)